Max Maievskyi

+49-1517-261-04-06 | MaksymMaievskyi@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/maksym-maievskyi | github.com/RedMaxMay

Current Location: Hamburg, Germany

SUMMARY

As a passionate Front-End Developer with a solid foundation in relevant technologies, I'm confident in my ability to add value to any development team. I want to apply my skills and knowledge to a full-time role as a Front-End Developer, where I can further develop my expertise and contribute to creating outstanding digital solutions. In addition to my technical skills, my decade of experience leading teams has increased my soft skills quite well, so I think I can contribute to the success of your company.

EDUCATION

Tel-Ran.de GmbH

React Frontend Developer

Kyiv National University of FT

Master's degree, Human Resources Management and Economics

Aug 2022 – Jun 2023 Berlin, Germany Sep 2008 – Aug 2013 Kyiv, Ukraine

Experience

Head of Department / Front-end Developer

Company: Art Expert LLC

Jan 2019 – Feb 2022

Kyiv, Ukraine

- Continued as a department manager, leading a team of 12 people $\,$
- Automated and optimized the department's work to achieve flawless results
- Learned HTML, CSS, and JS to create new e-commerce websites to grow the company
- Worked in a team to develop 2 e-commerce websites, a CRM, and a CMS:
 - * Collaborated with the team to design UI/UX
 - * Participated in the development of main pages, catalogs with sorting, shopping carts, and product pages and optimized everything for mobile devices (HTML, CSS, JS, Git, RestAPI).

Head of Department

Nov 2014 - Jan 2019

Company: Art Expert LLC

Kyiv, Ukraine

- Expanded the company and created a new department
- Increased sales and profitability by over 200% in 3 years
- Managed a team of 10 people (set goals, monitored task completion, trained and analyzed department performance, etc.)
- Developed strategies to increase company profitability, optimized workflows, and proposed new ideas for growth

Designer-Manager

Jul 2013 – Nov 2014

Company: Art Expert LLC

Kyiv, Ukraine

- Developed design solutions in Photoshop and Illustrator
- Expanded the company's client base through direct consultations and sales
- Contributed to the successful implementation of projects for restaurants and hotels
- Coordinated with the production department (created task lists and received completed work)

My Portfolio and Pet projects

PORTFOLIO | All projects with links to live demo and code on github

maxmay-portfolio.netlify.app

Last projects (description):

"Green Shop" | React, React Router, React Hooks, JavaScript, Semantic HTML5 markup, CSS custom properties, CSS Grid, Flexbox, Responsive Design, Axios, LocalStorage, CSS modules, REST API, Redux Toolkit

"Cars Info" | NextJS, TypeScript, React, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, Responsive Design, Firebase API, Cars API

"MaxMay Shop" | MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js), Mongoose, JWT, Responsive Design, React Bootstrap, Redux Toolkit, HTTP-Only cookies

"MaxMay Media" | React JS, React Hooks, JavaScript, Firebase API, Material UI, Material Icons, HTML5, CSS custom properties, Responsive Design, REST API

"Countries" | Mobile-first workflow, React, Styled Components, CSS custom properties, REST API, React Router

SKILLS

Technical skills: React, TypeScript, JavaScript, Redux, HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Responsive Design, Material UI, REST API, MySQL, MongoDB, Git, Node.js, Photoshop, Illustrator, UX/UI design

Soft skills: My experience as a team manager has helped me develop strong skills in leadership, communication, and problem-solving.

Languages: English (Professional Working Proficiency), Ukrainian (native), Russian (native)